### Project Structure

1. *Backend: Django Framework*
   - *Core App*: Handles general site settings, static pages (about, contact), and landing page.
   - *Accounts App*: Manages user registration, profiles, authentication, and permissions.
   - *Content App*: Manages different types of content (fan fiction, articles, reviews), and comments for each content.
   - *Newsletter App*: Handles subscriptions and email notifications.
   - *Ads App*: Manages Google AdSense integration and ad settings.

2. *Frontend:*
   - Use HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks like React or Vue.js for a dynamic user interface.
   - Ensure responsive design for mobile and desktop users.

### Detailed Breakdown of Each App

#### Core App
- *Models*:
  - SiteSettings: Site-wide settings like title, meta description, etc.
  - StaticPage: For static content like about and contact pages.

- *Views*:
  - HomeView: Renders the landing page.
  - StaticPageView: Renders static pages.
  - AboutView: Renders About page.
  - ContactView: Renders Contact page.

- *Templates*:
  - base.html: Base template for the site.
  - home.html: Home page template.
  - static_page.html: Template for static pages.
  - about.html: Template for about info.
  - contact.html: Template for site contact info

~#### Accounts App
- *Models*:
  - UserProfile: Extends the default user model with additional fields (bio, avatar, etc.).

- *Views*:
  - RegisterView: Handles user registration.
  - ProfileView: Displays user profiles.
  - LoginView and LogoutView: For authentication.
  - PasswordChangeView: For Changnig password.

- *Templates*:
  - register.html, profile.html, login.html, password_change.html, 

#### Content App
- *Models*:
  - Category: Specific model to define different category.
  - Genre: Specific model to define content genre.
  - Tag: Specific model to define content tag.
  - Content: Abstract base model for different types of content relating to different categories.

- *Views*:
  - ContentListView: Lists all content.
  - ContentDetailView: Displays detailed content view.
  - LikedContent: For likes.
  - DislikedContent: For dislikes.

- *Templates*:
  - content_list.html, single_post.html.

- *Admin*:
  - Customize admin to manage different content types efficiently.

- *I also want to handle comments in this app but I've not done it yet.*

#### Newsletter App
- *Nothing yet*

#### Ads App
- *Nothing yet*

### Functional Flow

1. *User Interaction:*
   - Users visit the site and land on the home page.
   - They can browse content categorized into fan fiction, articles, Books and others.
   - Users can register and log in to interact more deeply (e.g., comment, like and dislike, subscribe to newsletter).

2. *Content Management:*
   - Admins can create, update, and delete content through the admin interface.
   - Authors (Users in the Authors group) can access admin interface but can only submit new fan fiction, articles or other content, categories, tags or genres. They only have full control over content creation and modification through the admin interface.

3. *User Engagement:(Not done yet)*
   - Users can comment on and like or dislike content.
   - A newsletter subscription form allows users to subscribe for updates.

4. *Monetization:(Not done yet)*
   - Google AdSense ads are displayed in designated areas.
   - Ad settings can be managed through the admin interface.

5. *SEO and Analytics:(Not done yet)*
   - Implement SEO best practices across all templates.
   - Integrate Google Analytics to track user engagement and site performance.


Make it possible to share links to individual posts on social medie... With Meta content displayed